http://www.soccerincollege.com/privacy.aspx

Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on visits to our site and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: ;
To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs);
To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you);
To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs);
To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company
for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.;
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature; To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order
processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or
service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions
at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain
the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server.
All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be
accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private
information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies? Yes
(Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service
providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping
cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you
can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can
still place orders by contacting customer service.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise
transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business,
or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with
the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties
for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products
or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities
of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Childrens Online Privacy Protection
Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone
under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last reviewed on 02/29/2016
College Bound Athletes
Tour our Recruiting Platform
Ready to sign up? Click here
Showcase Tips
Are you ready for your next college showcase?
Soccer in College gave me a good point of reference for perspective coaches, somewhere I could direct them to see all of my data, in a well-organized, efficient manner. It was a good tool for my recruiting efforts.
- Thomas CurryWhat are others saying?
SoccerInCollege.com
for the sports minded student
SincSports.com
premier event management systems
Site Contents
Colleges
Tournaments
Leagues
© 2020|Privacy Policy1
My AccountLogin to view your accountSoccer in collegeCollegesTournamentsLeaguesTeamsAthletesUSA RankHow USA Rank worksView RankingsSincSportsSinc My TeamUpcoming EventsPromote Your EventHelp & SupportSearchable HelpContact UsContact UsLOGIN
LOGIN
0
SincSports Alert
